[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_B",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Crone's Curse",
        "Description": "Find any information pertaining to the whereabouts of the Corpse Crone.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The Corpse Crone is the next clue.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Careful not to give too much credit to the Azoth Tree - nature here does not always align with humanity's best interests. \\n\\nIf she exists, I suspect, however, the Corpse Crone may be hiding secrets of significant power.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Light be with you in Periville. \\n\\nI'll meet you outside of Karburg later.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I hope you had better luck than I, my friend. The legacy of the Corpse Crone seems to have claimed every town in this region. \\n\\nThe only thing I've learned about Ser Brytmar is that she departed from this area in some haste.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_C",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Curse of Karburg",
        "Description": "Discover what the Corpse Crone did to Karburg.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, we should search there next.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Perhaps. I've just come from searching Brytmar's home there. The Crone's curse swept through Karburg like a hurricane. \\n\\nIt appears the entire town fell Lost in hours, and the curse still haunts the streets like a contagion.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If there are clues to Brytmar's fate in this journal, I will find them.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hmmph! This journal tells more lies than truths! I simply cannot believe Brytmar would support this foul sorcery! \\n\\nWhat did you learn in Karburg? Did the Hunters manage to apprehend the Crone?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Bridge Into the Past",
        "Description": "Follow the Corpse Crone's studies on the Vega Bridge.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What about the Crone herself?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "If the journal is to be believed, the Crone spent centuries studying the Ancient ruins in the Fen. \\n\\nThat is undoubtedly where she acquired her power. The last entry makes specific mention of the ruins at Vega Bridge.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I refuse to believe Brytmar capable of conspiring with such evil.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The fact this rank stack of hovels stands as the last safe place in the Fen is testament to the Crone's evil legacy. \\n\\nLike Pennyfather, many here refuse to speak her name aloud… nor do they have word of Ser Brytmar.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_BellaRuby",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Weaver's Yarn",
        "Description": "Ask the citizens of Twillen about the Corpse Crone to pick up her trail.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I should ask around town as well.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You should. Unfortunately, many people lost faith in the knights during the Wars of Crimson Madness. \\n\\nYour inquiries about the Corpse Crone may get more honest answers. Meantime, I'm off to Hinbrucken.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Good luck getting straight answers from these people. You'll need it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, hello there! What brings you around these parts? Most people have better places to be than Weaver's Fen. \\n\\nBut for some of us, it's a safe refuge, a place where we can be who we want and live how we want.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_E",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Follow the Marsh Lights",
        "Description": "Follow the Marsh Lights to find the Corpse Crone's location.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So she's not just evil?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "No, but people need someone to blame for their misery, and they'll choose the easiest target. \\n\\nTo petition the Crone, follow the trail of torches on the south road… and be respectful! She has no patience for fools.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Whatever your purpose in seeking the Corpse Crone, I hope she aids you as she did me.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "At first, I didn't recognize her, and even now I doubt my eyes. She is much changed, but there can be no doubt. \\n\\nThat's the enchantress Morgaine... sister to Myrddin, the Crimson Sorcerer... and traitor to my lord king!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_E",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Temple of the Crone",
        "Description": "Destroy the Arcane Anchors Morgaine uses to power the barrier at her cave.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need to talk to her.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Indeed. Nothing could be more important! She believes she's safe behind this barrier, but I know her secrets. \\n\\nMyrddin used wards like this on his sanctum, and there's a way to break through them.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Quickly now! We must destroy the anchors before she can strengthen the wards.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Morgaine went to great lengths to protect her solitude… those anchors were farther than expected, but this barrier must come down. \\n\\nThough I goaded her into some dialogue, she's now back to ignoring me.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_B",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Face in the Mist",
        "Description": "Travel through the barrier at Morgaine's cave, tell her about your vision, and learn about Morgaine's past.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She confessed to all of it?",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I would hardly call it a confession! She has an explanation for everything, of course, as she always did. \\n\\nMoreover, I question the veracity of some of her claims - you must interrogate her as well.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If even half of what she claims is true, then things are far different than I imagined.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So you see now that I have neither insight nor responsibility in whatever fate befell the High King. \\n\\nAs to my part in my brother's fall, I have spent every moment  making amends… preparing for Corruption's eventual return.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_C",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Setting Aside Differences",
        "Description": "Convince Galahad that Morgaine's help is necessary before meeting Morgaine at Canopus.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That's why the Soulwardens need your help.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Well, of course you do! It would be a shame if I spent all this time and could offer no value to them. \\n\\nWait… you're a Soulwarden? I thought the Order perished… nevermind, we'll need all the help we can get.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I hope time has made Galahad more reasonable.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, perfect. Among these ruins, there are sources of power the Ancients learned to manipulate. \\n\\nOf most concern, the wells of pure azoth - Myrddin became obsessed with hoarding as much as he could.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Use of Azoth Energies",
        "Description": "Collect Ancient Shield Devices for Morgaine and meet her at the Ancient Device in Andrometus.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where do we start?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes. The fountain of pure azoth at this ruin dried long ago, but its residual power remains in the waters and in the Guardians who protect the site. \\n\\nWe must harness that power to recharge an Ancient warding apparatus nearby.",
        "InProgressResponse": "There should be several shield devices around Canopus. \\n\\nIf they aren't charged, you can siphon energy from the Ancient Guardians.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You handled that quickly and without complaint. It's been a long time since I partnered with someone so… competent. \\n\\nPeople disappoint - it's an unfortunate fact of nature. Only time will prove if you're an exception.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Unexpected Prisoner",
        "Description": "Explore Andrometus to discover what has been imprisoned there.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can check out the fault.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A glutton for danger, are you? I hope you have some measure of restraint… but at the moment, I'll take the bravado. \\n\\nThe fault could be caused by a threat the wards identified and contained.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Whatever's causing the fault in the eldritch boundaries, it must be remedied.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hm. Twice now, you solved problems without coming back to whine about some complication. \\n\\nWas there some entity that had been entrapped in the wards?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "CoatingAeternianT4",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Source of the Blight",
        "Description": "Follow the trail of Blight back to its Source for Morgaine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"There's more. I can investigate it.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, yes, yes. That adventurous spirit is definitely your weak spot, but once again, I'll take full advantage. \\n\\nI'll work on the wards while you track this... Blight back to its source. Do be careful.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Having second thoughts? If you want me to come with you, you'll have to wait some time.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I can tell from here that the ruin and the Angry Earth who resided there are riddled with the Blight. \\n\\nLet me guess - the azoth fountain within had been claimed by the Corrupted, by the Tempest?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Galahad_A",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Corruption Spreads its Hooks",
        "Description": "Travel back to Caer Dun to bring Yonus news from Morgaine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We'll need a larger force.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, of course, your fellow Soulwardens! It will be critical that we strike back against the Corrupted with both a martial and a magical strategy. \\n\\nTell me - where are you and your allies based? I will meet you there.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I hope we are not too late in our efforts to combat the Corrupted.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I am grateful to have you returned, Soulwarden. Hasty decisions have been made, and we need your insight.\\n\\nBut I know you've just returned from the Fen - has Morgaine agreed to join our cause?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
